through nature is spirit not body that
we are eternal being and God's love is
unconditional there's nothing we could
ever do to change that it is only our
illusion that we are separate from God
that we are in fact the reality is we
are one
now if that isn't a hazard to this
country you see my Forney how are we
going to keep building nuclear weapons
what's gonna happen to the arms industry
when we realize we're all one it's going
to fuck up the economy the economy
that's fake anyway which would be a real
bummer you know see why the government's
crackin down on the idea of experiencing
unconditional love
Henderson introducing the two drugs are
the legal alcohol cigarettes to drugs
and did absolutely nothing for you
whatsoever and drugs and naturally upon
this planet drugs that open your eyes up
to make you realize how you're being
fucked every day of your life those
drugs are against the law Wow
coincidence
I don't know
[Applause]
[Music]